Cleo A. Moursi

cleo6991@gmail.com | (646) 696-1096 | Portland, OR

Portfolio: cleyoga.wixsite.com/cleomoursi | LinkedIn: linkedIn.com/in/cleo-moursi-b1385a145/

UX Designer with a passion for accessibility. Certificate in UX/UI from the University of Oregon a and Master of Public Health Degree from the University of Michigan. Background in health and wellness translates well to empathizing with users. Experienced in web design and user research. Thrives on collaboration. An adaptable, quick learner with excellent organizational skills. A valuable addition to your team.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Coding: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, GitHub

UX/UI Tools: User Experience Interviewing, Persona Creating, Insight Synthesis, Journey Maps, Storyboards, A&B Testing, Heuristic Evaluations, Competitive Analysis, Wireframing, Responsive Web Design, Interactive Prototyping, Hi-Fi Mockups, Figma, Adobe XD

PROJECTS

Insurance Information Page: Streamlining the patient experience

I conducted user research then designed and wrote copy for a new site page outlining insurance information for prospective patients. Skills: User research interviews, Persona creation, Wireframing, Prototyping, Responsive web design, Figma

Poi Dog Rescue Nonprofit: A Redesign Project

The aim of this project was to improve site usability to increase the adoption rate of dogs from this nonprofit.

Skills: User research interviews and surveys, Persona creation, Storyboarding, Wireframing, Prototyping, Responsive web design, Figma

Washington Department of Licensing: A Redesign Project

This navigation-focused project simplified the layout of the homepage and shortened the user path to complete primary actions.

Skills: User research interviews, Persona creation, Information architecture, Wireframing, Prototyping, Figma

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Valeria Mallett Nutrition, LLC

Portland, OR

User Experience Consultant

January 2023-current

- Conduct user research by interviewing the practice staff and employees.
- Create prototypes of charting workflows, then iterate on them after further testing and review.
- Program charting templates in the practice's EHR to maximize each provider's patient-facing hours.
- Develop quick, user-friendly calculator shortcuts in JavaScript, improving provider efficiency during patient visits.

Registered Dietitian and Office Manger

July 2021-October 2022

- Counseled adult and pediatric patients over telehealth and in-person.
- Managed administrative staff team to ensure prompt, professional communication.
- Facilitated the advancement to a new electronic health record system.
- Implemented day-to-day website updates alongside the webmaster.

Pediatric Cardiology Center of Oregon

Portland, OR

Dec 2022-current

Registered Dietitian

• Counsel pediatric patients and their families on developing long-term, heart-healthy lifestyles.

- Create patient-focused, accessible materials to promote understanding and improve health literacy.
- Collaborate with patient's providers to ensure consistency and efficacy in treatment plans.

Cleo A. Moursi

cleo6991@gmail.com | (646) 696-1096 | Portland, OR

Portfolio: cleyoga.wixsite.com/cleomoursi | LinkedIn: linkedIn.com/in/cleo-moursi-b1385a145/

The Cleveland Clinic Cleveland, OH

Dietetic Intern

August 2020-July 2021

- Practiced dietetics in 7 different clinical specialties, including critical care, parenteral nutrition, and pediatrics, while receiving guidance and feedback from experienced preceptors.
- Presented case studies on each clinical specialty to the entire department, outlining how the nutrition care process was applied to unique and challenging patients.
- Developed proficiency in Epic EMR.
- Initiated a research study on total enteral nutrition protocols for adults with Crohn's Disease.

University of Michigan Recreational Sports Facilities

Ann Arbor, MI

Yoga Instructor

January 2016-March 2020

- Awarded Instructor of the Year in 2016.
- Taught weekly yoga classes for students, faculty, and staff of all levels in an inclusive way to promote emotional health as well as
 physical well-being.
- Mentored incoming yoga instructors to improve their skills and confidence in teaching for Rec Sports.

University of Michigan Health System

Ann Arbor, MI

Nutrition Education Volunteer

January 2019-April 2020

- Spearheaded a program inviting nutrition student volunteers to lead education sessions on nutrition and mental health at an outpatient psychiatric program to improve mentality surrounding food.
- Recruited and mentored additional nutrition student volunteers to expand the frequency of presentations and the breadth of topics discussed in the education sessions.

University of Michigan School of Public Health

Ann Arbor, MI

Family Food Study Research Assistant

April 2019-August 2019

• Conducted in-home field study visits and administered Food Frequency Questionnaires to mothers and their children to investigate the relationship between food insecurity and cognitive development.

PUBLICATIONS

Robbins AE, Tom C, Cosman M, Moursi C, Shipp L, Spencer TM, Brash T, Devlin MJ. (in press) Cold stress decreases trabecular bone mass in male C57BL/6J mice: implications for humans. *American Journal of Physical Anthropology*.

Devlin MJ, Robbins A, Cosman M, Moursi C, Cloutier AM, Louis L, Van Vliet M, Conlon C, and Bouxsein ML. (2018) Differential effects of high fat diet and diet-induced obesity on skeletal acquisition in female C57BL/6J vs. FVB/J Mice. *Bone Reports* 8:204-214. [open access]

EDUCATION

University of Oregon

Remote Live Classes

Certificate in UX/UI Design

November 2022-May 2023

University of Michigan School of Public Health

Ann Arbor, MI

Master of Public Health

University of Michigan College of Literature, Science, and the Arts

Ann Arbor, MI

Bachelor of Science in Anthropology